Bailey Schroder

♦ 2055 E Ranch Ct, Gilbert, AZ 85296 ♦ 913.314.3818 ♦ baileycschroder@gmail.com ♦

Objective

My passion for Mathematics has carried me through my education at Arizona State University, where I completed my bachelor's degree in, The College of Liberal Art's and Sciences. I have learned the importance of quantitative thinking, analytical problem-solving, and universal application. I find mathematical challenges so rewarding, driving my determination to solve problems successfully.

Professional Summary

I am a highly motivated professional with a strong background in data analysis and programming. My technical skills include proficiency in Excel, Python, C++, Java, SQL, MatLab, and Sharepoint. I excel in complex problem solving and critical thinking, allowing me to effectively manage IT projects and data, ensuring customer satisfaction. I am dedicated to efficient time management, and my experience in data analysis and programming equips me with the tools to drive success in a variety of technical roles.

Work Experience

Supply Chain Specialist

Amazon, Tempe, AZ

2023-Current

- Collaborating with cross-functional teams to optimize supply chain processes and ensure efficient inventory management.
- Utilizing data analysis and reporting tools to track key performance metrics. Conducting supplier audits maintaining highest standards.
- Managing procurement activities, including vendor relations, order processing, and inventory control to minimize stockouts and overstock situations.
- Negotiating favorable pricing while developing detailed documentation of supply chain processes and standard operating procedures (SOPs).

Digital/Data Analyst Intern Wine to Water, La Jolla, CA

2022-2023

- Conducted data analysis on digital marketing campaigns and customer behavior to identify trends and opportunities for optimization.
- Utilized tools such as Google Analytics, Excel, and data visualization software to create reports and dashboards for presenting key performance indicators.
- Cleaned, organized, and validated large datasets to ensure data accuracy and integrity.

Customer Service/Retail Specialist

FB Society, Scottsdale AZ

2015-2022

- Delivered exceptional customer service by addressing inquiries, resolving issues, and ensuring a positive shopping experience for customers.
- Trained new employees in customer service best practices and product knowledge to ensure a consistent customer experience.
- Adapted to fast-paced, high-pressure situations, and effectively resolved customer complaints to maintain customer loyalty.

Independent Business Owner

Salon Amore Gilbert, AZ

2015-2017

- Successfully launched and operated a Cosmetology business, including all aspects of business development, management, and customer service.
- Demonstrated strong entrepreneurial and business acumen.
- Managed financial aspects, including budgeting, financial forecasting, and profit and loss analysis.
- Continuously sought opportunities for improvement, innovation, and expansion of the business.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Mathematics Arizona State University Tempe, AZ [May, 2022]